<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>PHPTAL 1.1.8 released</title>
      <link>http://phptal.motion-twin.com/</link>
      <description>
		Fix and patch release
		- applied tal:repeat patch from Moritz Bechler
		- applied tales registry patch from Moritz Bechler
		- applied memory patch from 'smoking_birds_on_moon'
		- fixed setTemplate() reset existing prepared template (but not the context)
		- fixed ${structure foo} ${string:hello world}
		- added true: modifier support
		- added structure support to tal:attributes 
		</description>
      <dc:creator>Laurent Bedubourg</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2006-11-20</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHPTAL 1.1.9 released</title>
      <link>http://phptal.motion-twin.com</link>
      <description>
		Applied patch from Kornel Lesinski

		- Added phptal:cache that caches HTML of any given tag,
    		- Added phptal_tale() which returns chained TAL expressions as a single PHP expression. It's quivalent to phptal_tales(), but can be used in more contexts (i.e. ${foo | bar}),
    		- metal:fill-block can fill blocks in parent contexts,
    		- slightly improved runtime error messages.

		Other svn pending fixes:

    		- fixed "not" bug with complex php: expressions,
    		- fixed tales string backslash escaping,
    		- fixed only escape &lt; and &gt; in PCDATA,
    		- fixed php:$foo expression which is evaluated to php:${foo} equals $ctx-&gt;{$ctx-&gt;foo}.

		As annonced on the mailing like I don't have the time to maintain PHPTAL anymore, Kornel Lesinski kindly proposed himself to take the head of the project and we will plan the hand over during the following weeks. It was a pleasure to give this library to the community!

		Thanks to all PHPTAL users, Laurent Bedubourg
		</description>
      <dc:creator>Laurent Bedubourg</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2007-11-25</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHPTAL 1.1.10 released by new maintainer</title>
      <link>http://phptal.motion-twin.com</link>
      <description>
 The latest release adds more robust error handling and integrates PHPTAL a bit better with PHP SPL:
 
 • added support for Countable and ArrayAccess SPL interfaces,
 • added support for superglobals in php: TALES expressions,
 • changed default temp directory to use sys_get_temp_dir(). If this causes trouble, you can override it using define('PHPTAL_PHP_CODE_DESTINATION','/tmp/');
 • added additional safety-checks to code generation and macro execution to prevent invalid templates from triggering PHP errors,
 • fixed small bugs in XML parser,
 • fixed few error messages to be more precise and report proper file/line,
 • changed all exceptions thrown by PHPTAL to inherit PHPTAL_Exception.
      </description>
      <dc:creator>Kornel Lesinski</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2008-01-26</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHPTAL 1.1.11 released</title>
      <link>http://phptal.motion-twin.com</link>
      <description xml:space="preserve">
 Handy feature, less bugs.
       	    
 • nothing or NULL as last alternative in tal:attributes will cause attribute to be omitted entirely,
 • support for systems on which sys_get_temp_dir() does not include trailing slash,
 • fixed warning when clearing cache.
      </description>
      <dc:creator>Kornel Lesinski</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2008-01-29</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHPTAL 1.1.12 released</title>
      <link>http://phptal.motion-twin.com</link>
      <description xml:space="preserve">
 New RepeatController by Iván “DrSlump” Montes:
  • based on SPL iterators (to simplify the code),
  • added support for string iteration,
  • added support for letter and roman properties,
  • added support for grouping first and last properties,
  • most properties are computed as needed.

 PHPTAL is now easier to use as part of a framework or a plug-in:
  • Required files are included from directory pointed by PHPTAL_DIR constant (it's defined automatically). This makes it easier to use multiple copies of PHPTAL, and eliminates need for include_path.
  • Configuration can be changed without using constants (patch by Werner): 
      $t = PHPTAL::create('index.html')
        ->setPhpCodeDestination('application/tmp/')
        ->setPhpCodeExtension('tmp')
        ->setForceReparse(true)
        ->set('title', 'My Title')
        ->set('heading', 'My Heading');

 These changes are backwards-compatible: PEAR installations are unaffected, configuration constants are still supported.
      </description>
      <dc:creator>Kornel Lesinski</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2008-04-17</dc:date>
    </item>
       <item>
         <title>PHPTAL 1.1.13 released</title>
         <link>http://phptal.motion-twin.com</link>
         <description xml:space="preserve">   
 • New template cleanup routines based on patch by Sergio Chersovani. PHPTAL will now clean up all old template files and will recompile templates also when their timestamp changes to an older one.
 • Added support for PHP constants in TALES.
 • Improved parsing of XML with syntax errors after root node. If you start getting errors about text after root node, wrap your templates in a &lt;tal:block&gt; element.
 • Improved parsing of semicolons in PHP strings, tal:attributes and tal:define.
 • Fixed parsing of backslash escapes in TALES strings (bug reported by Josh Duck)
 • New configuration methods now work properly with external macros (bug reported by Philip Reichenberger)
 • Added workaround for protected __isset/__get (problem reported by Anru Chen)
</description>
         <dc:creator>Kornel Lesinski</dc:creator>
         <dc:date>2008-07-27</dc:date>
       </item>    
  </channel>
</rss>
